Finding Aid for the Joseph Byrne Lockey Papers LSC.0127
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Central America
  - 4. Central America, 1841
    - MacDonald, A. to [William J. Murphy]. Government House, December 6, 1841.; 64.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/30). (Box 1)
    - Maskall, William and G.D. Adolphus. Statement, December 7, 1841.; 65.; 6pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/32). (Box 1)
    - Hall, William to Earl of Aberdeen. British Consulate, Guatemala, December 8, 1841.; 66.; (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/25). (Box 1)
    - MacDonald, A. to Sir C. Metcalfe Bart. British Honduras, Government House, Belize, December 18, 1841.; 67.; (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/32). (Box 1)
    - Morales, Juan to The Superintendent, Belize. Government House, Camayagua, December 31, 1841.; 68.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/32). (Box 1)
  - 5. Central America (Guatemala, Nicaragua, British Honduras, etc.), 1842
    - Notes and Lists of Foreign Office Documents., 1.; 8pp. (pencil - 7 × 9 ruled paper). (Box 1)
    - Hall, William to The Earl of Aberdeen. British Consulate, Guatemala, January 2, 1842.; 2.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/29). (Box 1)
    - White, Thomas to Henry Goulburn. Epperstone Rectory, Nottingham, January 11, 1842.; 3.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/30). (Box 1)
    - MacDonald, A. to The Earl of Aberdeen. British Honduras, Government House, Belize, January 11, 1842.; 4.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/29). (Box 1)
    - Note., 5.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/29). (Box 1)
    - Extract from a despatch from W.I. Murphy to His Excellency Colonel MacDonald dated Guatemala, January 29, 1842.; 6.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/31). (Box 1)
    - Orosco, Simon to The Superintendent, Honduras. Department of Relations, Government House, Leon, January 30, 1842.; 7.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/32). (Box 1)
    - Willock, M.H. to Captain Higginson. Barque Little, Catherine, Kingston, February 11, 1842.; 8.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/31). (Box 1)
    - MacDonald, A. to Lord Stanley. British Honduras, Government House, Belize., 9.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/31). (Box 1)
    - Metcalfe, C.T. to Colonel MacDonald. Jamaica, Kings House, March 30, 1842.; 10.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/31). (Box 1)
    - Aberdeen to Con General Chatfield. Foreign Office, April 13, 1842.; 11.; 7pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/29). (Box 1)
    - Adam, Charles and Alexander MacDonald, to J.C. Fitzgerald. Belize, Honduras, April 15, 1842.; 12.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/31). (Box 1)
    - [Unknown] to His Excellency The Chief of the State of......... British Honduras, Belize, April 16, 1842.; 13.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/31). (Box 1)
    - Adam, Charles to J.C. Fitzgerald. Illustrious off Belize, April 16, 1842.; 14.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/31). (Box 1)
    - Adam, Charles to Sir C.T. Metcalfe. Illustrious off Belize, British Honduras, April 23, 1842.; 15.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/31). (Box 1)
    - Adam, Charles to The Honorable Sidney Herbert, M.P. Illustrious at Sea, Lat: 24.28. N. Long: 86.41 West, April 29, 1842.; 16.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/31). (Box 1)
    - Stanley to Lord Elgin. Downing Street, May 13, 1842.; 17.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/32). (Box 1)
    - Adam, Charles to Sidney Herbert, M.P. Illustrious off Belize, British Honduras, June 19, 1842.; 18.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/32). (Box 1)
      - Garciones, Jose Miguel, to Charles Adam. Government House, San Jose, May 17, 1842.; 1.; 7pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/32). (Box 1)
    - Bell, Jas. Stanislaws to The Earl of Elgin. North Blewfields, Mosquito Shore, October 1842.; 19.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/30). (Box 1)
      - Copy of Depositions made before the Magistrate at North Blewfields in, respecting the former condition and Supremacy of the Southern portion of the Mosquito Shore., October 1842; 1.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/30). (Box 1)
    - Chatfield, Frederick to Charles Adam. British Consulate General, Leon, November 16, 1842.; 20.; 7pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 252/8). (Box 1)
    - Chatfield, Frederick to The Earl of Aberdeen. Central America, Leon, November 21, 1842.; 21.; 5pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/29). (Box 1)
    - Chatfield, Frederick to the Principal Secretary of the Supreme Government of the State of Nicaragua. British Consulate General, Leon, November 15, 1842.; 22.; 9pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/29). (Box 1)
    - Chatfield, Frederick to the Earl of Aberdeen. Central America, Guatemala, December 24, 1842.; 23.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/29). (Box 1)
  - 6. Costa Rica, 1848-49
    - Calvo, to [Unknown]. Casa De Gobno, San Jose, October 19, 1848.; 1.; 6pp. (Copy, photostat, of Foreign Office 97/88). (Box 1)
    - Molina to Palmerston. 81 Gloucester Terrace, London, March 17, 1849.; 2.; 5pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 21/2 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 1)
    - Molina, F, January 12, 1849.; 3.; (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 21/2 - 7 × 9 red margin paper) 1p. (Box 1)
    - Molina to Palmerston. 81 Goucester Terrace, Hyde Park, December 23, 1848.; 4.; 9pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 21/1 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 1)
    - Christie, W.D. to Señor Calvo. San Jose, September 26, 1848.; 5.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of Foreign Office 97/88). (Box 1)
  - 7. Costa Rica, 1862-65
    - Riotte, C.N. to William H. Seward. Legation of the U.S.A., Costa Rica, San Jose, May 15, 1862.; 1.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Despatches from Costa Rica, vol.1 - Desp. no.32). (Box 1)
      - Enclosure no.1-32, from San Jose, Costa Rica (Copy from Miscellaneous Correspondence., May 15, 1862; 1.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
      - Enclosure no.2-32, from San Jose, Costa Rica., May 15, 1862; 2.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Riotte, C.N. to William H. Seward. Legation of the U.S.A., Costa Rica, San Jose, May 15, 1862.; 2.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Dispatches from Costa Rica, vol.1. Dispatch no.33). (Box 1)
      - Enclosure no.33, from San Jose, Costa Rica. Iglesias, Francisco M. to C.N. Riotte., May 15, 1862; 1.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Riotte, C.N. to William H. Seward. Legation of the U.S.A., Costa Rica, San Jose, June 10, 1862.; 3.; 14pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Dispatches from Costa Rica, vol.1 Dispatch no.36). (Box 1)
    - Riotte, C.N. to William H. Seward. Legation of the U.S.A., Costa Rica, San Jose, August 27, 1862.; 4.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Dispatches from Costa Rica, vol.1 Dispatch no.44). (Box 1)
      - Enclosure no.1-44, from San Jose, Costa Rica. Transcript from Register Miscell. Corresp., August 27, 1862; 1.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
      - Enclosure no.2-44, from San Jose, Costa Rica. Iglesias, Francisco M. to Minister of Foreign Relations of the Republic of Costa Rica., August 27, 1862; 2.; 9pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Riotte, C.N. to William H. Seward. Legation of the U.S.A., Costa Rica, San Jose, December 13, 1862.; 5.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Dispatches from Costa Rica, vol.1 Dispatch no.53). (Box 1)
      - Enclosure no.1-53, from San Jose, Costa Rica. Iglesias, Francisco M. to Minister of Foreign Relations of the Government of the Republic of Nicaragua., December 13, 1862; 1.; 3pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
      - Enclosure no.2-53, from San Jose, Costa Rica. Translation., December 13, 1862; 2.; 5pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
      - Enclosure no.3-53, from San Jose, Costa Rica. Riotte, C.N., December 13, 1862; 3.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Riotte, C.N. to William H. Seward. Legation of the U.S.A. Costa Rica, San Jose, July 13, 1863.; 6.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Dispatches from Costa Rica, vol.2 Dispatch no.76). (Box 1)
      - Enclosure 1-76 from San Jose, Volio, J. to C.N. Riotte., July 13, 1865.; 1.; 1p. (typewritten). (Box 1)
      - Enclosure 2-76 from San Jose, Riotte, C.N. to J. Volio., July 13, 1865.; 2.; 2pp. (typewritten). (Box 1)
      - Enclosure no.3-76 from San Jose, Riotte, C.N. to A.B. Dickinson., July 13, 1865.; 3.; 2pp. (typewritten). (Box 1)
    - Riotte, C.N. to William H. Seward. Legation of the U.S.A., Costa Rica, San Jose, July 27, 1863.; 7.; (Copy, typewritten, of Dispatches from Costa Rica, vol.2) 1p. (Box 1)
    - Riotte, E.N. to William H. Seward. Legation of the U.S.A., Costa Rica, San Jose, October 13, 1863.; 8.; (Copy, typewritten, of Dispatches from Costa Rica, vol.2 Dispatch no.86). (Box 1)
    - Riotte, C.N. to William H. Seward. Legation of the U.S.A., Costa Rica, San Jose, April 19, 1865.; 9.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Dispatches from Costa Rica, vol.2 Dispatch no.121). (Box 1)
      - Enclosure no.1-121, San Jose, Riotte, C.N., April 19 1865.; 1.; 3pp. (typewritten). (Box 1)
  - 8. Costa Rica, 1847-58
    - Note., 1.; Typewritten (white paper 8.5 × 11). (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to Al Ministro de Relaciones del Salvador., 2.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, 8.5 × 14 paper). (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to A los Sres. Delegados a la Dieta Nacional de Centro-America en Nacaome, August 5, 1847.; 3.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to El Comandante del Puerto de Moin al Norte de este Estado, October 4, 1847.; 4.; 1p. (Box 1)
    - [Unknown] al Senor Ministro de Relaciones de Nicaragua, October 20, 1847.; 5.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to los Gobernadores de Veracruz y el Istmo, March 17, 1848.; 6.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo Al Ministro de Micaragua, March 20, 1848.; 7.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to Señor Dn. Federico Chatfield, Consul General de S.M.B. en Centro-America., 8.; 1p. Typewritten. (Box 1)
    - [Unknown] al Señor Don Luiz Beschor, April 14, 1848.; 9.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - [Unknown] to Mntro. de Nicaragua, April 22, 1848.; 10.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - [Unknown] to Ministro de Relaciones de Honduras, May 5, 1848.; 11.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to Comandante del Puerto de San Juan, May 15, 1848.; 12.; 1p. Typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to Ministro de Nicaragua, May 20, 1848.; 13.; 2pp. Typewritten. (Box 1)
    - [Unknown] to Señor Don Federico Chasfiel, Consul general de S.M.B. en Centro America, July 20, 1848.; 14.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to Señor Consul, October 8, 1848.; 15.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to Señor Coronel Don Ricardo Wright., 16.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to Señor W. De Christie Consul Britanico Mosquito El Presidente de la Republica, October 1848.; 17.; 3pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to Ministro Plenipot°, March 14, 1849.; 18.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - [Unknown] to Ministro Plenipotenciario de la Republica en Europa, April 13, 1849.; 19.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to A S.E. el Señor E. George Squier Ministro Plenipotenciario del Gobno. de los Estados Unidos cerca de los de Centro-America, July 16, 1849.; 20.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - [Unknown] to Mnistro de Nicaragua, September 5, 1849.; 21.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to Ministro de Guatemala, September 20, 1849.; 22.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Jaoquin Bernardo to Señor E. George Squier Mntro. Plenipotenciario de los Estados Unidos, October 20, 1849.; 23.; 3pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to Señor don Felipe Molina, Ministro de Costa Rica en Londres, December 15, 1849.; 23.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to Señor don Felipe Molina, Ministro en Londres, December 15, 1849.; 24.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to Señor E. George Squier Mintro. Plenipotenciario de los Estados Unidos, November 20, 1849.; 25.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to He. Señor Federico Chatfield Encargado de Negocios de S.M.B. en la Republica de Costa Rica, December 3, 1849.; 26.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to los Sres. Don Federico Chatfield y Don Felipe Jaurequi, December 29, 1849.; 27.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to Señor Don F. Jauregui Enviado Extraordinario del Gobno. de Honduras, December 31, 1849.; 28.; 3pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to Señor Lic. don Felipe Molina, Ministro Plenipotenciario en Londres, April 15, 1850.; 29.; 3pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to Licenciado don Felipe Molina, Ministro Plenipotenciario en Europa, May 15, 1850.; 30.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to Lic. don Felipe Molina, Ministro Plenipotenciario ante varios Gabinetes de Europa, October 8, 1850.; 31.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to señor don Felipe Molina, Ministro Plenipotenciario en Europa, December 9, 1850.; 32.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to señor don Felipe Molina, September 19, 1852.; 33.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to don Felipe Molina, November 9, 1852.; 34.; 3pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, J.B. to Don Felipe Molina, Ministro de Costa Rico en Europa y los Estados Unidos de America, July 1853.; 35.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo to Señor don Felipe Molina., 36.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - [Unknown] to don Felipe Molina, Ministro en Europa y Estados Unidos, March 22, 1854.; 37.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - [Unknown] to los Plenipotenciarios en Washington, December 25, 1857.; 38.; 4pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - [Unknown] to los Ministros Plenipots. de Costa Rica en Washington, February 1, 1858.; 39.; 4pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - [Unknown] to A La fond - E, March 30, 1853.; 40.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - [Unknown] to Don Luis Molina, May 26, 1858.; 41.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - [Unknown] to Señor La fond, July 31, 1858.; 42.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - [Unknown] to Señor Don Luiz Molina., 43.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - [Unknown] to don Luis Molina, August 31, 1858.; 44.; 3pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - [Unknown] to A. Lafond, September 1, 1858.; 45.; 5pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
  - 9. Costa Rica (Duplicate of no.8 Above)
  - 10. Dispatches and Instructions (Miscellaneous), 1858-64
    - Cass, Lewis to Mirabeau B. Lamar. Department of State, Washington, (Instructions to American States, vol.15 no.2)., January 2, 1858; 1.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Cass, Lewis to Mirabeau B. Lamar. Department of State, Washington, (Instructions to American States, vol.16 no.17)., December 1, 1858; 2.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
      - Enclosure 17, to Mirabeau B. Lamar. Memoranda of conversations with Lord Napier., December 1, 1858; 1.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
      - Enclosure 17, to Mirabeau B. Lamar. Memorandum of conversation with M. de Sartiges., December 1, 1858; 2.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Seward, William H. to A.B. Dickinson. Department of State, Washington, (Instructions to American States, vol.16 no.17)., March 7, 1862; 3.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Seward, William H. to E.O. Crosby. Department of State, Washington, (Instructions to American States, vol.16 no.10)., April 7, 1862; 4.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Seward, William H. to E.O. Crosby. Department of State, Washington, (Instruction to American States, vol.16 no.12)., May 9, 1862; 5.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Seward, William H. to Charles N. Riotte. Department of State, Washington, (Instructions to American States, vol.16 no.18.)., June 4, 1862; 6.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Seward, William H. to A.B. Dickinson. Department of State, Washington, (Instructions to American States, vol.16 - Unofficial.)., August 25, 1862; 7.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Seward, William H. to Charles N. Riotte. Department of State, Washington, (Instructions to American States, vol.16 no.25)., September 17, 1862; 8.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Seward, William H. to Elisha O. Crosby. Department of State, Washington, (Instructions to American States, vol.16 no.30)., October 9, 1862; 9.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Seward, William H. to Charles N. Riotte. Department of State, Washington, (Instructions to American States, vol.16 no.65)., November 10, 1863; 10.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Seward, William H. to Charles N. Riotte. Department of State, Washington, (Instructions to American States, vol.16 no.71)., February 10, 1864; 11.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Lamar, Mirabeau B. to Lewis Cass, Secretary of State. Legation of the United States, Managua (Dispatches from Nicaragua and Costa Rica, vol.3 Dispatch no.10)., May 28, 1858; 12.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Lamar, Mirabeau B. to Lewis Cass. Legation of the United States, Managua, (Dispatches from Nicaragua and Costa Rica, vol.3 no.11.)., June 24, 1858; 13.; 6pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Lamar, Mirabeau B. to Lewis Cass, Legation of the United States, Managua, (Dispatches from Nicaragua and Costa Rica, vol.3 no.12.)., June 26, 1858; 14.; 2pp. (typewritten). (Box 1)
    - Lamar, Mirabeau B. to Lewis Cass. Legation of the United States. Leon, (Dispatches from Nicaragua and Costa Rica, vol.3 no.21.)., July 1858; 15.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Lamar, Mirabeau B. to Lewis Cass. Legation of the United States, Managua, (Dispatches from Nicaragua and Costa Rica, vol.3 no.17)., July 9, 1858; 16.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Lamar, Mirabeau B. to Lewis Cass. Legation of the United States, San Jose, (Dispatches from Nicaragua and Costa Rica, vol.3 Dispatch no.25)., September 29, 1858; 17.; 4pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Lamar, Mirabeau B. to Lewis Cass. Legation of the United States, On Board the Merrimac, Harbor of Realejo, (Dispatches from Nicaragua and Costa Rica, vol.3 no.33)., December 22, 1858; 18.; 5pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Dimitry, Alexr. to Lewis Cass, Legation of the U.S. in Nicaragua, Managua, (Dispatches from Nicaragua and Costa Rica, vol.5)., January 30, 1860; 19.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
    - Dimitry, Alexr. to William Henry Prescot, Actg. Secretary of State, Washington. Legation of the United States, San Jose, Costa Rica, (Dispatches from Nicaragua and Costa Rica, vol.6 no.22)., August 6, 1860; 20.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
      - Enclosure 22 from San Jose, Esquivel, A. to H.E. Alexr. Dimitry., August 6, 1860.; 1.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
      - Enclosure 22 from San Jose, Gomes, F. to The Minister of Foreign Relations of the Government of the Republic of Costa Rica., August 6, 1860.; 2.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
      - Hall, Edward to the Licentiate Don Crecencio Gomez., 3.; 2pp. typewritten. (Box 1)
      - Alvarado, Casto to Mr. Minister of the Treasury and of War of the Supreme Government of the Republic. Republic of Honduras., 4.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 1)
  - 11. Diplomatic Representatives to Central America (British), 1825-34
    - Extract of letter from Colonel Cockburn to Viscount Goderich. Government House, Honduras, July 10, 1832.; 1.; 1p. typewritten (7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 1)
    - Extract of letter from William Hall to John Bidwell. British Consulate, Guatemala, August 15, 1832.; 2.; 1p. typewritten (7 × 9 red margin paper - copy of Foreign Office 15/12). (Box 1)
    - List of British Consuls to Central America and Guatemala., 3.; 1p. typewritten (7 × 9 ruled paper). (Box 1)
    - Extracts from letters of George Canning to John O'Reilly. Foreign Office, July 5, 1825.; 4.; (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/4 - 7 × 9 ruled paper). (Box 1)
    - Extract from a letter from Joseph Planta to G.A. Thompson. Foreign Office, September 9, 1825.; 5.; (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/1 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 1)
    - Extract from Report of G.A. Thompson at Guatemala to Joseph Planta. Foreign Office, October 19, 1825.; 6.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/1 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 1)
    - Extract from Report of G.A. Thompson to The Right Honorable George Canning. London, December 3, 1825.; 7.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/1). 7 × 9 red margin. (Box 1)
    - O'Reilly, John to Señor Juan Francisco Sosa. Consulado Britanica, January 25, 1826.; 8.; 1p. (Typewritten, Foreign Office 15/5 - 7 × 9 red margin paper. (Box 1)
    - [O'Reilly, John] to George Canning. British Consulate, Guatemala, February 22, 1826.; 9.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/5 - 7 × 9 ruled paper). (Box 1)
    - Translation of a speech by the President of the Federation on the opinion of the Session of the Congress Enclosure in Mr. O'Reilly's despach no.5 of Guatemala, March 18, 1826. March 1, 1826.; 10.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/5). 7 × 9 red margin paper. (Box 1)
    - Extract of letter from E.W.H. Schenley to Joseph Planta. Edinburgh, July 24, 1826.; 11.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/5) 7 × 9 ruled paper. (Box 1)
    - [O'Reilly, John], Dispatch. British Consulate, Guatemala, April 7, 1827.; 12.; 2pp. typewritten (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/7 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 1)
    - [Backhouse, John] to [Mr. Schenley]. Foreign Office, January 14, 1828.; 13.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/8 - 7 × 9 ruled paper). (Box 1)
    - [Mr. Schenley] to [John Backhouse]. 5 Upper Baker St, February 16, 1828.; 14.; (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/8. 7 × 9 red margin paper. 1p). (Box 1)
    - [Backhouse, John] to [Mr. Schenley]. Foreign Office, March 6, 1828.; 15.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/8 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 1)
    - Extracts of letter from the Earl of Dudley to Mr. Consul Dashwood, Guatemala. Foreign Office, May 19, 1828.; 16.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/8). (Box 1)
    - [Dashwood, Colonel] to [John Backhouse], March 10, 1830.; 17.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/8 - 7 × 9 ruled paper). (Box 1)
    - [Schenley] to [Colonel Dashwood], February 7, 1829.; 18.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/8). 7 × 9 red margin. (Box 1)
    - Extract of letter from Colonel Dashwood to John Backhouse, Secretary of State. British Consulate, Guatemala, March 10, 1830.; 19.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/10 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 1)
    - Note., 20.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/10 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 1)
    - [Dashwood, Colonel] to [Viscount Palmerston]. British Consulate, [Guatemala], April 18, 1831.; 21.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/11). (7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 1)
    - Lord Ely, brother-in-law of Colonel Dashwood, to Viscount Palmerston. Kirtlington Park, June 26, 1831.; 22.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/11 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 1)
    - [Hall, William] to [John Bidwell]. British Consulate Guatemala, August 3, 1831.; 23.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/11 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 1)
    - [Ely, Marchsoniss of] to [Lord Palmerston. Ely Lodge, Enniskillen, August 9, 1831.; 24.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/11 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 1)
    - [Backhouse, John] to [Consul Dashwood]. 1p. Foreign Office, August 13, 1831.; 25.; (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/11 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 1)
    - [Dashwood]. Extract of letter from George Dashwood to Lord Palmerston. Davenport, December 19, 1831.; 26.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/11 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 1)
    - [Backhouse, J.]. Note, February 18, 1832.; 28.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/11). (7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 1)